Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory6 Mss.B.B61.inventory06
American Philosophical Society
Franz Boas Papers: Inventory (H)
1862-1942
Mss.B.B61.inventory06
American Philosophical Society
1.0 section
This is part of the large inventory for the Franz Boas Papers (Mss B B61). For complete information concerning this collection, please view the Collection Description.
Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
Scope and Contents note
Due to the size of the collection, the content for Series I has been divided into multiple inventories. Please follow the links below to browse the inventories.
Inventories
Correspondents A
Correspondents B
Correspondents C
Correspondents D
Correspondents E-G
Correspondents H
Correspondents I-K
Correspondents L
Correspondents M
Correspondents N-Q
Correspondents R
Correspondents S
Correspondents T-V
Correspondents W-Z
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents H
  - Haas (Box 35)
    - Haas -- to Akademie der Wissenschaften im Wien (See enc: Korkhof, Franz, Aug. 9, 1932)
  - Haas, Albert (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 12; 4p
  - Haas, Alfred (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 20; 1p
  - Haas, Arthur (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 31; 2p
  - Haas, Mary R. (Box 35)
    General note
    See also Swadesh, Morris
    - 1937 Nov 22, 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Sept. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 May 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 May 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 July 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 14; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 July 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - See Boas, F.(open letter) Jan. 6, 1941, 1941 Jan. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - M.R. Haas -- to B. Edel, 1939 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - M. R. Haas -- to E. Sapir, 1937 June 9; 2p.
  - Haase, Miss F.L. (Box 35)
    - See Speyer, James -, 8-24-20
  - Habas, Ralph A. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 19; 1p.
  - Haber (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 3; 1p.
  - Haberer, A. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 20; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 20; 1p.
  - Haberlandt, Arthur (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 26; 2p.
  - Haberlandt, Michael (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 20; 2p.
  - Hackeling, F.A. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 27
  - Hackley (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1907 May 11
  - Haddon, Alfred C. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1905 June 25
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 May 21
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 22
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 May 23; (telegram
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 7; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 6; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1907 June 14
    - To Boas, 1907 July 11
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1908 Sept. 11; Postcard
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 July 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 July 11
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 3; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 24; 2p.
    - A.C. Haddon -- to Gerda Lebbelon, 1910 Dec. 15; 2p.
  - Hadenburg, Elsa (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 12; 2p.
  - Hadin, P. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 14
    - Hadl, R., 1917 May 31; 1p.
  - Hadley, Arthur T. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 May 14; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1906 May 1
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 May 2
    - To Boas, 1906 May 28
    - To Boas, 1907 June 6
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 20; 1p.
  - Hadley, J.N. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 16; 1p.
  - Hadlfon (?) (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 7
  - Hadony? (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 13; 1p.
  - Haebeling, F. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 27; 2p.
  - Haeberlin, Hermann (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1918 July 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 July 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 July 22; 2p.
    - (Enc. with Boas, F. to Feddersen, K.F. of same Date), 1918 Aug. 7; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 31; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Sept. 24; 2p.
  - Haeberlin, Hermann K. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 20
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 17
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Sept. 16
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept. 21
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept. 25
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 7; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 30; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 4; 2p.
  - Haeckel, Ernst Walter (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 22; 4p.
  - Haessler, Luise (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 19
  - Haffberg? (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 15; postcard
  - Hafner, A. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 6
  - Hagar, Stansbury (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1914 Sept. 24
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 7
    - S. Hagar -- from E.J. Brill, 1920 Sept. 4; 1p.
  - Hagedorn, Hermann Jr. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 8; 1p.
  - Hagemeyer, F.H. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 16; 1p.
  - Hagen, B. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1923
  - Hague, E. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1909 Sept. 20
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 12
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 13
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 27; 1p.
  - Hahn, B.R. (Box 35)
    - B.R. Hahn -- to C. Razovsky, 1938 July 22; 2p.
    - (Enc. with Razovsky, C., July 27, 1938)
  - Hahn, Frida K. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 June 21; 1p.
    - See Santa Fe, Laboratory of anthropology Application blank for F.K. Hahn, Mar. 4, 1930.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc: Report. 8p.), 1933 Sept. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 2; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 10; 3p.
  - Hahn, Hans (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 June 19
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 12; 2p.
  - Hahnlandt, A. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 30; 2p.
  - Haile, B. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 July 14; 1p.
  - Haines, Anna J. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1930 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 17; 1p.
      Scope and Contents note
      (Enc: Pamphlet)
  - Haines, Maria F. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 12
  - Haiti. Secretaire d'Etat de l'Instruction Publique (Box 35)
    - From McConnell, H. Ormonde, 1940 Nov. 30
  - Haiti Journal (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 9; 1p.
  - Hakim, J. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 1; 1p.
  - Halacki, O. de (Box 35)
    - See League of Nations (to the council and members of the League), Nov. 4, 1922
  - Halbert, A. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 24; 2p.
  - Hale, Everett E. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 31; 1p.
  - Hale, George E. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 7
    - From Boas, 1917 June 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar.; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 May 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 6; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 14; 3p.
  - Hale, Horatio (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1888 Sept. 18
    - From Boas, 1889 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1889 Mar. 13; 8p.
    - From Boas, 1889 Mar. 21
    - From Boas, 1889 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1889 July 6
    - From Boas, 1889 July 25
    - From Boas, 1889 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1890 May 2
    - From Boas, 1894 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1894 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1894 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1887 end
    - To Boas, 1887 end
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 1; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 25; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 30; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1888 May 7; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1888 May 14; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 May 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 May 21; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1888 May 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 May 7?; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1888 June 14; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 June 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 July 4; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 July 7; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1888 July 13; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Sept. 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Sept. 17; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Sept. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 3; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 8; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 18; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 31; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 20; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 8; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 27; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 4; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 22; 11p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 4; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 11; 13p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 19; 12p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1889 June 8
    - To Boas, 1889 June 27
    - To Boas, 1889 July 12; 12p.
    - To Boas, 1889 July 12; (telegram
    - To Boas, 1889 July 13; 12p.
    - To Boas, 1889 July 16; (postcard
    - To Boas, 1889 July 29; (telegram
    - To Boas, 1889 July 30
    - To Boas, 1889 July 30; (telegram
    - To Boas, 1889 July 31
    - To Boas, 1889 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1889 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1889 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1889 Sept. 12
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 10; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 23; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1889 end
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1890 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1890 Feb. 14; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1890 May 7; postcard
    - To Boas, 1890 May 13
    - To Boas, 1890 May 15; postcard
    - To Boas, 1890 May 21
    - To Boas, 1890 May 25; postcard
    - To Boas, 1890 May 26
    - To Boas, 1890 June 21
    - To Boas, 1890 June 25
    - To Boas, 1890 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1890 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1890 Sept. 8
    - To Boas, 1890 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1890 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1890 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1890 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1890 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1890 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1890 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1891 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1891 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1891 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1891 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1892 Jan. 23; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1892 Apr. 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1893 Aug. 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1894 June 5
    - To Boas, 1894 June 22
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 13
    - To Boas, 1894 Sept. 1
    - To Boas, 1894 Sept. 15
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 20
    - H. Hale -- to G.M. Clinton Dawson, 1888 Nov. 26; 4p.
  - Hale, R.T. (Box 36)
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanallas, Feb. 11, 1937
  - Halecki, Oscar (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1942 May 12; 1p.
  - Halem, Otto von (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 2
  - Hales, Frank N. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1903 June 1; 2p.
    - F.N. Hales -- to Major Powell, 1903 Feb. 11; 4p.
    - F.N. Hales -- to Holmes, 1903 June 9; 2p.
  - Haliburton, R.G. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 14
  - Hall, Agnes (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 15
  - Hall, Alfred I. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1886 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1889 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1890 Feb. 14
  - Hall, Allen (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 28; 1p.
      (Enc: Hall, A. Outline of study of inherited nature and instinctive interest)
  - Hall, Ansel Franklin (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec.; 12p.
  - Hall, Edward H. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 11; 1p.
  - Hall, Edwin H. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 10; 2p.
  - Hall, G.F. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - (Enc: Sauerland, C. Report on Milk Fund., Jan. 23, 1934)
    - Hall, G.F. Re: Citizens' mutual aid committee.), 1934 Apr. 11; 2p.
    - (Enc. with Hall, G.F. Mar. 2, 1934), 1935 Apr. 15; 1p.
  - Hall, G. Stanley (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1888 Oct.; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1889 Aug. 20
    - From Boas, 1889 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1889 Oct. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1891 June 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 July 2
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 7
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 27; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Aug. 8
    - To Boas, 1889 Aug. 30; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1890 Sept. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1891 Apr. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1891?
    - To Boas, 1909 June 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1920 July 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 31; 1p.
  - Hall, Martin (Box 36)
    - See Schroetter, Erich von., Nov. 22, 1938
    - To Boas, 1939 end; 1p.
  - Hall, N. Brigham (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 16
  - Hall, P.F. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 28
  - Hall, R.D. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 1; 1p.
  - Hall, T.G. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 23
  - Hall, T. Proctor (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1891 July 9
  - Hall, T.W. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 27; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 18; 2p.
  - Halle, Fannina W. (Box 36)
    - F.W. Halle -- from H.A. Moe, 1942 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 6; 1p.
      (Enc: Vita and publications)
  - Haller, D. (Box 36)
    Same as Haller, Ludwig
    - To Boas, 1885 Dec. 29
  - Haller, Ludwig (Box 36)
    s.a. Haller, "D."
    - To Boas, undated; 4p.
    - To Boas, undated; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1887 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 5
  - Halliday, W.H. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - W.H. Halliday -- to W.E. Ditchburn, 1930 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - (Enc. with Fairbairn, A.M.D., Dec. 8, 1930)
    - (Attached to Ditchburn, W.E. to British Columbia Governor Dec. 5, 1930, 1930 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Fairbairn, A.M.D., Dec. 19, 1930)
  - Hallinan, C.T. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1919 May 9; 1p.
  - Halloch, William (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 4; 1p.
  - Hallock, William (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 12; 1p.
  - Hallowell, A.I. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 8; 2p.
    - A.I. Hallowell -- from E.R.A. Seligman, 1927 Oct. 20
  - Hally (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 18
  - Halpern, Irving W. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1935 July 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 11; 1p.
  - Ham, Roswell G. (Box 36)
    - See Baker, Frank E. (open letter), 1939 Dec.
  - Hambergisches Welt-Wirtschafts- Archiv. Hamburg, Germany (Box 36)
    See Stuhlmann, [Franz]
  - Hambly, W.D. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept. 24; 1p.
  - Hambruch, P. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 22; 1p.
  - Hamburg-American Line (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Aug. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 12; 1p.
      See Meyer, Julius P.
  - Hamburg-American Packet Co. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 21
  - Hamel, A. van (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 25; 1p.
  - Hamilton, Alice (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 4; telegram
  - Hamilton, Elisabeth B. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1936 July 9; 1p.
  - Hamilton, George L. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1909 May 25
    - To Boas, 1913 May 28; 2p.
  - Hamilton, J.P. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 2; 1p.
  - Hamilton, John S. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 21; 1p.
  - Hamilton, Samuel L. (Box 36)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938.
  - Hamlin, A.D.F. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 4; 2p.
  - Hamm (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 20
  - Hammerich (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 13; telegram
  - Hammett, Dashiell (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939
    - (See Brewster, Dorothy July 18, 1939), 1940 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan.; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 12; 1p.
      (Enc: In Defense of the Bill of Rights)
  - Hammond, J.H. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 29; 4p.
  - Hammond, John Jr. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Hammond Typewriter Co. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 15
  - Hampson, Thomas (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1887 July 21
    - To Boas, 1887 July 28